imcdb.org 2019-12-17

# IMCDb.org: Help/FAQ

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by IMCDb.org and how it is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at the address contact@imcdb.org.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, IMCDb.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes IP addresses, type of browser, date/time stamp and referring pages. More information such as Internet Service Provider (ISP), country, list of visited pages and number of clicks to analyze trends, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information are collected via [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html "Google Analytics' privacy policy") (you can [opt out if you wish](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "How to opt out of google analytics")).

We do not make any link between the information stored in the server logs, the information collected and managed by Google Analytics and your user profile on the site (if you have one).

## Cookies

IMCDb.org does use cookies to store information to customize Web page content. The following information are stored:

  * Selected langage
  * Nickname and password, in case the "Auto-login" option is enabled
  * Image resizing options, when submitting pictures to the site

## Personal information provided

To register on the site, providing a valid e-mail address is mandatory. This address is stored in our database but will never be provided to any thrird-party. We may use it in case the site administrator needs to contact you personally and individually, but you will not receive generic e-mail such as newsletters or advertising without your prior consent. If you wish to remove this e-mail address from our database, you can do so by simply editing your profile.

Other information that you may enter in your user profile and/or in the comments on the site are publicly displayed and so you are responsible for these. Please be aware that once something is posted in public, these information can be re-used and re-posted by other people, so do not publish anything you may want to make disappear later.

In case you wish to delete your account to remove your username from our members list and anonymize the messages linked to it, simply contact us at the address mentioned at the beginning of this page.

## Advertising System Cookies

We may allow “third-party” entities such as ad servers, ad networks and data collection organizations, to place and utilize cookies on IMCDb.org. Cookies enable third-parties to present ads to users based on their visit to IMCDb.org and other sites on the Internet. 

These third-parties use technology to deliver advertisements that appear on IMCDb.org directly to your web browsers. These third-parties automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, Javascript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-parties to measure the effectiveness of advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

IMCDb.org has no access to or control over cookies and technologies that are used by third-party advertisers. IMCDb.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers, networks and data collection organizations for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options or by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) industry website at: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can also be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Our main advertising partner is PubGalaxy, you can [find here their privacy policy](https://www.pubgalaxy.com/privacy-policy.html).

## Facebook

Facebook provide a "Like" button shown on the home page and on each vehicle page. To do so we embed code that they provide and we do not control ourselves. To function their buttons generally know if you’re logged in; for example Facebook use this to say “x of your friends like this”. We do not have any access to that information, nor can we control how Facebook use it.
